Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. New York Office. Media Center Audiovisual Collection, 1953-2015 and undated RL.00734
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Optical Media (CDs, DVDs), 1993-2015; undated; 4
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--16 spots, 2007 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0663)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--11 spots: Cadbury, Diageo, Domino's, Unilever, 2007 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0664)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT New York Non-Traditional Storytelling, 2007 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0665)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--15 spots: JetBlue, Halls, Domino's, Kraft, ESPN, American Red Cross, Nike, MTV, Fox Sports, Nintendo, 2007 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0666)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT New York Non-Traditional Storytelling, 2007 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0667)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Creativity and Ad Age Happy Hour Reel, 2007 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0668)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Graham's Atmospheres and Textures, 2007 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0669)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Best of the Best, 2007 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0670)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT New York Non-Traditional Storytelling, 2007 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0671)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Brand Jordan, 2007 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0672)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Winning Songs, 2007 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0673)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--CD Audio 18 songs, 2007 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0674)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--11 Spots: Johnson and Johnson, Domino's, Kimberly Clark, Jenny Craig, Trident, HSBC, Smirnoff, Stride, 2007 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0675)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Trident, Smirnoff, Ilori, 2007 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0676)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT Cannes Incentive, 2007 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0677)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT New York Non-Traditional Storytelling, 2007 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0678)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--HSBC Live Window Theater, 2007 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0679)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT New York Traditional Storytelling, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0680)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT New York Reel for David, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0681)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--HSBC Work, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0682)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Non-Traditional Master, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0683)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Best of Reel, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0684)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Trident 2005-2007, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0685)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JNJ Agency Reel New York and Global: Schick Wilkinson, JetBlue, DTC, HSBC, Domino's, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0686)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT Global Reel, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0687)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Integration Presentation: Budweiser, FedEx, Bridgestone, Doritos, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0688)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Current Creative Work, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0689)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT New York Non-Traditional Storytelling, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0690)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT New York Non-Traditional Storytelling, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0691)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--DTC: ADIF Roses case study and integrated campaign revised, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0692)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--DTC: ADIF Roses case study and integrated campaign final, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0693)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Stride Q2 Case Study, Integrated Case Study, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0694)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--DTC Diamonds Website Navigation, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0695)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Stride Q2 Case Study, Integrated Case Study, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0696)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--DTC Diamonds Website Navigation New Version, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0697)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--DTC Diamonds Website Navigation Old Version, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0698)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--New Case Studies and Presentation Video, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0699)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Non-Traditional Storytelling, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0700)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT New York Non-Traditional Storytelling, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0701)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT New York Non-Traditional Storytelling, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0702)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--TV Recruitment Reel, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0703)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Recruitment Reel, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0704)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Non-Traditional Storytelling, 2008 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0705)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT New York Non-Traditional Storytelling, 2009 (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0706)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Video Cases and Agency Video, Undated (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0707)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--SGH Global Pitch, Undated (Box O10, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0708)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT New York Proprietary Storytelling: Sundance, Lovebites, The Nursery, 2008 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0709)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT New York Proprietary Storytelling: Sundance, Lovebites, The Nursery, 2007 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0710)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT New York Proprietary Storytelling: Sundance, Lovebites, The Nursery, 2008 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0711)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT New York Proprietary Storytelling: Sundance, Lovebites, The Nursery, 2007 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0712)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Original Content: Sundance, Flex N Zephyr, Lovebites, 2007 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0713)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Buddy Lee Story, 2008 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0714)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Buddy Lee Man of Action, 2008 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0715)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Ty Montague Weiden and Kennedy Work Originals, Undated (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0716)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Weiden + Kennedy 7-11 Manifesto, Undated (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0717)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Ty Archive 02 Artwork Duplicate, Undated (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0718)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Ty Archive 03 M+Book Duplicate, Undated (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0719)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Ty Archive 05 Scans, Undated (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0720)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Recruitment Reel, 2008 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0721)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--TV Recruitment Reel, 2008 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0722)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--JWT New York Traditional Storytelling, 2006 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0723)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Best of the Best: rough and not in order, 2007 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0724)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Alternate Options, 2007 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0725)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--7 and Above Reel: Radio, TV, Creative Innovation, Media, Digital, 2008 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0726)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Worldwide Creative Council 6s or Better, 2008 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0727)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Winners DVD Round 1, 2008 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0728)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--17 Spots: Cannes and One Show Winners, 2008 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0729)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Q2 Showcase, 2010 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0730)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Q4 Showcase, 2008 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0731)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Q1 Showcase Reel, 2009 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0732)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Q1 Showcase Reel, 2008 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0733)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--2009 C3 Global Creative Showcase, 2010 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0734)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Clio Awards: Kleenex, Halls, Rolex, Sunsilk, Domino's, Undated (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0735)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Andy Awards, 2009 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0736)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Effies 2007: Stride (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0737)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Rolex Kelly Awards, 2006 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0738)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Danny and David Young Guns, Undated (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0739)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Contract Mumbai, Worldwide Creative Council Master, 2009 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0740)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Contract Mumbai, Worldwide Creative Council Backup, 2009 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0741)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Contract Bangalore, Entries for Cannes Shortlist, 2009 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0742)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Contract Chennai, Worldwide Creative Council Cannes Shortlist, 2009 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0743)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Contract Advertising New Delhi, Cannes Worldwide Creative Council, 2009 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0744)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Strategy Conference, 2009 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0744a)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--WPP Presentation: Nestle, Nokia, DTC, Band-Aid, Kit Kat, MTV, 2009 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0745)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--WPP Presentation: Nestle, Nokia, Band-Aid, Kit Kat, MTV, 2009 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0746)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Cannes 2007 Film Bronze Lions (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0747)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Cannes 2007 Film Grand Prix, Gold and Silver Lions (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0748)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Cannes 2007 Titanium and Integrated Lions and Shortlists (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0749)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Cannes 2007 Direct, Media, Promo and Ambient Lions (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0750)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Cannes 2007 Unilever Lions (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0751)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Cannes/One Show Winners, 2008 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0752)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Cannes/One Show Winners, 2008 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0753)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Sunsilk Cannes Award Submission Original Cut, 2007 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0754)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Sunsilk Cannes Award Submission Lovebites Rough Cut, 2007 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0755)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Sunsilk Cannes Award Submission Lovebites Innovation Content and Context, 2007 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0756)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Cannes Incentive, 2007 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0757)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Cannes Lions DVD 1: Winners, Film Lions, 2008 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0758)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Cannes Lions DVD 2: Winners, Press Lions, Outdoor, Radio, Titanium and Integrated, 2008 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0759)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Cannes Lions DVD 3: Winners Direct, Media, Promo, Cyber, Design, 2008 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0760)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Cannes Submisisons Master, 2008 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0761)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Cannes Bike Video, 2008 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0762)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Disc 1: Film Lions Winners; Young Lions Film; Film Jury Cup; Special Awards, 2010 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0763)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Disc 3: Winners, Young Lions, Jury Video Clips, Special Awards, 2010 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0764)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Disc 1: Film Lions Winners; Young Lions Film; Film Jury Cup; Special Awards, 2009 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0765)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Disc 2: Winners, Young Lions, Jury Video Clips, Special Awards, 2009 (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0766)
  - Bob Jeffrey Video Library--Cannes Master Disc, Undated (Box O11, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0767)
- Video, 1955-2008; undated; 5
  - AAAA Fifty Years of Free TV, 1995 (Box U1, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-001)
  - AAAA Self Regulation, 1984 (Box U1, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-002)
  - Adcraft reel, 1998 (Box U1, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-003)
  - AICP Show, 2000 (Box U1, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-004)
  - Allen's Picks 1998 Creative Standards (Box U1, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-005)
  - Argentina--Classic Commercials, Undated (Box U1, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-006)
  - Argentina--Commercials (PAL), 1998 (Box U1, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-007)
  - Argentina--Commercials, 1998 (Box U1, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-008)
  - Argentina--Commercials en Ingles, 1997 (Box U1, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-009)
  - Argentina--Commercials, 1998 (Box U2, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-010)
  - Argentina--Historical Ford Commercials, Undated (Box U2, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-011)
  - Argentina--Reel Commerciales Miniphone (NTSC), Undated (Box U2, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-012)
  - Argentina--Subtitled commercials (NTSC), Undated (Box U2, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-013)
  - Asia Pacific--Showreel Best Work WWEG, 1996 (Box U2, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-014)
  - Asia Pacific--1st Quarter Reel, 1998 (Box U2, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-015)
  - Asia Pacific--1st Quarter Review Tape 1, 1998 (Box U2, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-016)
  - Asia Pacific--1st Quarter Review Tape 2, 1998 (Box U2, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-017)
  - Asia Pacific--2nd Quarter Reel, 1998 (Box U2, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-018)
  - Asia Pacific--3rd Quarter Review, 1998 (Box U3, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-019)
  - Asia Pacific--4th Quarter, 1998 (Box U3, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-020)
  - Association of Italian Handicapped; Chilean Red Cross. U.S. format, Undated (Box U3, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-021)
  - Austrian Airlines "It Flies, It Flies" TVC 40 (NTSC), 1998 (Box U3, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-022)
  - Bally's/Health and Tennis spots, Undated (Box U3, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-023)
  - Bangkok Hughes--Peter Hughes Asia Pacific 1st quarter``, 2000 (Box U3, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-024)
  - Bangkok Hughes, Undated (Box U3, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-025)
  - Bell Atlantic "Betty", Undated (Box U3, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-026)
  - Bell Atlantic Small Business Website, Undated (Box U3, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-027)
  - Best Commercials of Latin America, 1998 (Box U4, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-028)
  - Best spots and worst spots, 1997 (Box U4, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-029)
  - The Big Picture no. 2, 1995 (Box U4, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-030)
  - Board of Directors JWT Europe and Asia Pacific Best of 1994 (Box U4, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-031)
  - Brouillard--Jim Foster update on Brouillard Communications, 1986 (Box U4, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-032)
  - Chicago--A Look at JWT Chicago, Undated (Box U4, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-033)
  - Chicago--Hancock Center/Funny tour film, 1980 (Box U4, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-034)
  - Chicago--Hugh Roberts "Effective Kraft Advertising 1985-1986" (Box U4, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-035)
  - Chile--Case History M. Educacion campana 1983; Antonio Sarroca (Box U4, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-036)
  - Chile--The Iceberg Theory, Undated (Box U5, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-037)
  - Clairol--Woman to Woman compilation reel, 1995 (Box U5, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-038)
  - Client Group Meeting Chicago (NTSC), 1998 (Box U5, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-039)
  - Competitive Analysis of Ogilvy & Mather; presentation to Board of Directors, 1986 (Box U5, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-040)
  - Creative Standards--Other TV commercials from master reel that were not used for WPP Board reel, 1998 (Box U5, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-041)
  - Credo intro, Undated (Box U5, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-042)
  - Czech Republic--Organics Total Branding, 1997 (Box U5, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-043)
  - DeBeers Engagement spots, Undated (Box U5, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-044)
  - Detroit--Adcraft reel, 1996 (Box U5, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-045)
  - DeBeers reel, Undated (Box U6, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-046)
  - Detroit--Adcraft reel, 1996 (Box U6, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-047)
  - Detroit--CNN news coverage of Ford sponsorhip of Schlinder's List movie on TV "public relations", Undated (Box U6, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-048)
  - Detroit--Dream Cars of the 50s and 60s (vintage tv commercials and sales films), Undated (Box U6, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-049)
  - Detroit--Ford 50th Anniversary, Undated (Box U6, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-050)
  - Detroit--Ford auto/truck casting reel, 1992 (Box U6, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-051)
  - Detroit--Funny stuff/Dealer bull, Undated (Box U6, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-052)
  - Detroit--Goodyear Tire and Rubber international commercials, 1995 (Box U6, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-053)
  - Detroit--Issue #1, 1988 (Box U6, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-054)
  - Detroit--Madison Ave. satire 3 1/2 min., Undated (Box U7, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-055)
  - Detroit--Tristate Ford Dealer Association Get It Taurus, 1995 (Box U7, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-056)
  - Detroit--Old reel 11 spots, Undated (Box U7, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-057)
  - Detroit--Peter Schweitzer Brand Speech Adcraft, 1993 (Box U7, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-058)
  - Detroit--Peter Schweitzer Brand Speech Adcraft, 1993 (Box U7, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-059)
  - Detroit--United Way Day One, Undated (Box U7, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-060)
  - Detroit--Untitled, Undated (Box U7, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-061)
  - Detroit--Weekly reel (FDAF) 8/21-11/17, 2000 (Box U7, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-062)
  - Detroit--Weekly reel (FDAF) 3/19-6/11, 2001 (Box U8, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-063)
  - Detroit--Weekly reel (FDAF) 6/18-9/3, 2001 (Box U8, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-064)
  - Detroit--Weekly reel (FDAF) 9/10-10/8, 2001 (Box U8, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-065)
  - Detroit--Weekly reel (FDAF) 10/15-11/12, 2001 (Box U8, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-066)
  - Detroit--Weekly reel (FDAF) 11/12-12/17, 2001 (Box U8, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-067)
  - Detroit--Weekly reel (FDAF) 11/30-3/12, 2001 (Box U8, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-068)
  - Detroit--Weekly reel (FDAF) 1/7-2/4, 2002 (Box U8, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-069)
  - Detroit--Weekly reel (FDAF) 3/4-4/29, 2002 (Box U8, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-070)
  - Detroit--Weekly reel (FDAF) 5/6-6/17, 2002 (Box U9, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-071)
  - Dick Razor presentation European Managers, 1974 (Box U9, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-072)
  - Don Johnston Biltmore tape, 1974 (Box U9, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-073)
  - Don Johnston and Denis Lanigan remarks in honor of Subhas Ghosal's retirement, 1985 (Box U9, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-074)
  - Eastman Kodak "Wedding" :45, Undated (Box U9, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-075)
  - Epcot--Amsterdam new business (PAL), 1984 (Box U9, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-076)
  - Epcot--Amsterdam new media development, 1984 (Box U9, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-077)
  - Epcot--Chicago "Beat Us", 1984 (Box U9, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-078)
  - Epcot--Chicago "Ol Blue Eyes", Undated (Box U9, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-079)
  - Epcot--Chicago secretaries' reel, 1980 (Box U10, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-080)
  - Epcot--Chicago Secretaries' Week "All My Secretaries", 1982 (Box U10, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-081)
  - Epcot--Chicago softball, 1981 (Box U10, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-082)
  - Epcot--Chicago "Warriors", Undated (Box U10, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-083)
  - Epcot--Chicago "Xmas film", 1974 (Box U10, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-084)
  - Epcot--Frankfurt "Eigendarstellung", Undated (Box U10, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-085)
  - Epcot--London ECS presentation personnel training, 1983 (Box U10, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-086)
  - Epcot--London close-up for U.S. offices, 1983 (Box U10, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-087)
  - Epcot--London Kit Kat poster scans, 1983 (Box U11, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-088)
  - Epcot--Madrid new business, 1984 (Box U11, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-089)
  - Epcot--Mexico 40th anniversary "4 decadas de musica mexicana" television special, 1984 (Box U11, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-090)
  - Epcot--New York, National Secretaries' Week "J. Walter Secretary", 1983 (Box U11, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-091)
  - Epcot--New York Office Christmas party, 1982 (Box U11, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-092)
  - Epcot--New York, SRI International "American Portrait" 25:00, 1983 (Box U11, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-093)
  - Epcot--Paris new business (PAL), 1984 (Box U11, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-094)
  - Epcot--Sao Paulo Sam Meek seminar, 1983 (Box U11, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-095)
  - Epcot--Sao Paulo sales promotion, 1984 (Box U11, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-096)
  - Epcot--Sydney new business JWT Enterprise, 1984 (Box U12, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-097)
  - Epcot--Tokyo commercials, 1984 (Box U12, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-098)
  - Epcot--Tokyo DeBeers "Kigyo saizen Sen", 1984 (Box U12, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-099)
  - Epcot--Washington U.S. Marine Corps "Combat Options", 1984 (Box U12, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-100)
  - Epcot--Washington U.S. Marine Corps "Rose Garden", 1984 (Box U12, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-101)
  - Epcot--Washington U.S. Marine Corps "Such as Regiments Hand Down Forever", 1984 (Box U12, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-102)
  - Europe, Middle East and Africa Creative League Table, 1999 (Box U12, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-103)
  - Europe 1st trimester advertising, 1995 (Box U12, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-104)
  - European new creative work EXCO (NTSC), 2000 (Box U12, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-105)
  - Europe showreel (NTSC), 1993 (Box U13, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-106)
  - Europe showreel (NTSC), 1999 (Box U13, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-107)
  - EXCO reel Cannes, 2000 (Box U13, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-108)
  - Eyes on Thompson Orientation Week, Undated (Box U13, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-109)
  - FDAF Newark F Series Hummingbird/Columbus newspaper/Cleveland Flip Up Escort, Undated (Box U13, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-110)
  - FDAF Lincoln Mercury presentation reel, 1992 (Box U13, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-111)
  - FDAF Outdoor presentation tape, 1995 (Box U13, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-112)
  - FDAF reel for Blaise Newman, 1996 (Box U13, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-113)
  - Ford Division Dealer Show San Francisco, 1996 (Box U13, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-114)
  - Frankfurt--Siemens C25 9 versions, 1999 (Box U14, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-115)
  - Frankfurt--Siemens C25 international product launch, 1999 (Box U14, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-116)
  - Frankfurt--Siements products tape 1, 1999 (Box U14, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-117)
  - Frankfurt--Siements products tape 2, 1999 (Box U14, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-118)
  - Frankfurt--Siemens SL10 Vanessa Mae; Jean Paul Gaultier, Undated (Box U14, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-119)
  - Global Agency Network reel, 2000 (Box U14, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-120)
  - Greece--Police Force "Grandmother" :30, Undated (Box U14, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-121)
  - Health and Tennis (Bally) 32 spots, 1990 (Box U14, Video-cassette RL00734-Umatic-122)